<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title></title>
 <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href=""/>
 <updated>2014-01-04T00:40:12+11:00</updated>
 <id></id>
 <author>
   <name></name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>What did I learn yesterday?</title>
   <link href="/hello/2013/09/28/easy-form-optimisation.html"/>
   <updated>2013-09-28T00:00:00+10:00</updated>
   <id>/hello/2013/09/28/easy-form-optimisation</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Bronnie Ware is an Australian nurse who spent many years working in palliative care caring for those who were dying. She eventually published a book called the The Top Five Regrets of the Dying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joining a larger company is never easy and we learned a number of invaluable lessons along the way. We learned the importance of teamwork and a strong relationship with corporate leadership. We learned to leverage the innovations Conduit was creating, while adding our own unique voice, skills and capabilities to the Conduit team. Wibiya&amp;#8217;s team and technology are powering innovation across many Conduit products and has created a significant impact across the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Conduit’s new direction and organizational changes, the Wibiya platform is no longer in alignment with the future strategy. Over the coming months, most of the Wibiya team and innovations will be integrated throughout Conduit, bringing our expertise and experience to existing and yet-to-be released products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In appreciation of your loyalty, Conduit will be offering all Wibiya publishers three free months of Conduit Mobile. Conduit Mobile is a dynamic platform that allows anyone to easily create a mobile app or mobile site. Wibiya publishers will receive an email with additional information in a few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>What did I learn today?</title>
   <link href="/hello/2013/08/28/what-did-I-learn.html"/>
   <updated>2013-08-28T00:00:00+10:00</updated>
   <id>/hello/2013/08/28/what-did-I-learn</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;My emotional states shape my attitude. My attitude shapes my experience. When I smoke weed, I get a new perspective. When I use x, I am very happy, friendly and comfortable to be myself around people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The feelings emerge from using stimulants and they only there for a limited time. With the observing self, I can learn from these experiences and change consciously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although, I don&amp;#8217;t feel how I felt on Friday now, I can still remember it. I had the will and strength to dig deeper into the nagging feelings that I had around being with Anna and sex. Suddenly everything made sense. I don&amp;#8217;t remember how the thought process was but the feeling of peace, relaxation and love was right there. Here&amp;#8217;s what I can recall;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anna is a very important part of my life. I never wanted to have sex with someone although our sex life is hanging of the cliff. Thinking about someone feels like I am conflicting myself, although I don&amp;#8217;t know why yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a duty to myself to be the person that I want to be. I feel this is my opportunity to grow mindfully and be someone that I am 100% happy to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two are not conflicting with each other they are just tangled. There is a risk associated with changing personalities in terms maintaining my relationship with Anna. However, I feel like that risk can be mitigated if I keep the communication lines open with her and if she does the same too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Friday I was free from the nagging internal talk and I was happy. I don&amp;#8217;t know how but i even managed to hangout with people that didn&amp;#8217;t speak english. I had good time with my brothers and other people that we met casually.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class='highlight'&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class='ruby'&gt;&lt;span class='o'&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class='n'&gt;html&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class='o'&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;span class='k'&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class='nf'&gt;foo&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class='nb'&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class='s1'&gt;&amp;#39;foo&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class='k'&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>What did I learn, if I ever learned anything?</title>
   <link href="/hello/2013/08/28/test-test.html"/>
   <updated>2013-08-28T00:00:00+10:00</updated>
   <id>/hello/2013/08/28/test-test</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;My emotional states shape my attitude. My attitude shapes my experience. When I smoke weed, I get a new perspective. When I use x, I am very happy, friendly and comfortable to be myself around people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The feelings emerge from using stimulants and they only there for a limited time. With the observing self, I can learn from these experiences and change consciously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class='highlight'&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class='ruby'&gt;&lt;span class='lineno'&gt;1&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class='k'&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class='nf'&gt;foo&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class='lineno'&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;   &lt;span class='nb'&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class='s1'&gt;&amp;#39;foo&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class='lineno'&gt;3&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class='k'&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although, I don&amp;#8217;t feel how I felt on Friday now, I can still remember it. I had the will and strength to dig deeper into the nagging feelings that I had around being with Anna and sex. Suddenly everything made sense. I don&amp;#8217;t remember how the thought process was but the feeling of peace, relaxation and love was right there. Here&amp;#8217;s what I can recall;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anna is a very important part of my life. I never wanted to have sex with someone although our sex life is hanging of the cliff. Thinking about someone feels like I am conflicting myself, although I don&amp;#8217;t know why yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a duty to myself to be the person that I want to be. I feel this is my opportunity to grow mindfully and be someone that I am 100% happy to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two are not conflicting with each other they are just tangled. There is a risk associated with changing personalities in terms maintaining my relationship with Anna. However, I feel like that risk can be mitigated if I keep the communication lines open with her and if she does the same too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Friday I was free from the nagging internal talk and I was happy. I don&amp;#8217;t know how but i even managed to hangout with people that didn&amp;#8217;t speak english. I had good time with my brothers and other people that we met casually.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>