<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
<<<<<<< HEAD
 <title>Ali Yalcin Kaya</title>
 <link href="http://yalcinkaya.github.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://yalcinkaya.github.com"/>
 <updated>2014-01-04T00:35:24+11:00</updated>
 <id>http://yalcinkaya.github.com</id>
=======
 <title></title>
 <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href=""/>
 <updated>2014-01-04T00:40:12+11:00</updated>
 <id></id>
>>>>>>> parent of 52506de... tagline update
 <author>
   <name>Ali Yalcin Kaya</name>
   <email>kayayalcin@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
<<<<<<< HEAD
   <title>What did I learn yesterday?</title>
   <link href="/hello/2013/09/28/easy-form-optimisation.html"/>
   <updated>2013-09-28T00:00:00+10:00</updated>
   <id>/hello/2013/09/28/easy-form-optimisation</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Bronnie Ware is an Australian nurse who spent many years working in palliative care caring for those who were dying. She eventually published a book called the The Top Five Regrets of the Dying.&lt;/p&gt;
=======
   <title>Helloworld</title>
   <link href="http://yalcinkaya.github.com/lessons/2013/02/17/helloworld"/>
   <updated>2013-02-17T00:00:00+11:00</updated>
   <id>http://yalcinkaya.github.com/lessons/2013/02/17/helloworld</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;hey&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Jekyll Introduction</title>
   <link href="http://yalcinkaya.github.com/lessons/2011/12/29/jekyll-introduction"/>
   <updated>2011-12-29T00:00:00+11:00</updated>
   <id>http://yalcinkaya.github.com/lessons/2011/12/29/jekyll-introduction</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This Jekyll introduction will outline specifically what Jekyll is and why you would want to use it. Directly following the intro we&amp;#8217;ll learn exactly &lt;em&gt;how&lt;/em&gt; Jekyll does what it does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id='overview'&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id='what_is_jekyll'&gt;What is Jekyll?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll is a parsing engine bundled as a ruby gem used to build static websites from dynamic components such as templates, partials, liquid code, markdown, etc. Jekyll is known as &amp;#8220;a simple, blog aware, static site generator&amp;#8221;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id='examples'&gt;Examples&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This website is created with Jekyll. &lt;a href='https://github.com/mojombo/jekyll/wiki/Sites'&gt;Other Jekyll websites&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id='what_does_jekyll_do'&gt;What does Jekyll Do?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll is a ruby gem you install on your local system. Once there you can call &lt;code&gt;jekyll --server&lt;/code&gt; on a directory and provided that directory is setup in a way jekyll expects, it will do magic stuff like parse markdown/textile files, compute categories, tags, permalinks, and construct your pages from layout templates and partials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once parsed, Jekyll stores the result in a self-contained static &lt;code&gt;_site&lt;/code&gt; folder. The intention here is that you can serve all contents in this folder statically from a plain static web-server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can think of Jekyll as a normalish dynamic blog but rather than parsing content, templates, and tags on each request, Jekyll does this once &lt;em&gt;beforehand&lt;/em&gt; and caches the &lt;em&gt;entire website&lt;/em&gt; in a folder for serving statically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id='jekyll_is_not_blogging_software'&gt;Jekyll is Not Blogging Software&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jekyll is a parsing engine.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll does not come with any content nor does it have any templates or design elements. This is a common source of confusion when getting started. Jekyll does not come with anything you actually use or see on your website - you have to make it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id='why_should_i_care'&gt;Why Should I Care?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll is very minimalistic and very efficient. The most important thing to realize about Jekyll is that it creates a static representation of your website requiring only a static web-server. Traditional dynamic blogs like Wordpress require a database and server-side code. Heavily trafficked dynamic blogs must employ a caching layer that ultimately performs the same job Jekyll sets out to do; serve static content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore if you like to keep things simple and you prefer the command-line over an admin panel UI then give Jekyll a try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developers like Jekyll because we can write content like we write code:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to write content in markdown or textile in your favorite text-editor.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Ability to write and preview your content via localhost.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;No internet connection required.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Ability to publish via git.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Ability to host your blog on a static web-server.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Ability to host freely on GitHub Pages.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;No database required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id='how_jekyll_works'&gt;How Jekyll Works&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following is a complete but concise outline of exactly how Jekyll works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be aware that core concepts are introduced in rapid succession without code examples. This information is not intended to specifically teach you how to do anything, rather it is intended to give you the &lt;em&gt;full picture&lt;/em&gt; relative to what is going on in Jekyll-world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learning these core concepts should help you avoid common frustrations and ultimately help you better understand the code examples contained throughout Jekyll-Bootstrap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id='initial_setup'&gt;Initial Setup&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After &lt;a href='/index.html#start-now'&gt;installing jekyll&lt;/a&gt; you&amp;#8217;ll need to format your website directory in a way jekyll expects. Jekyll-bootstrap conveniently provides the base directory format.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id='the_jekyll_application_base_format'&gt;The Jekyll Application Base Format&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll expects your website directory to be laid out like so:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;.
|-- _config.yml
|-- _includes
|-- _layouts
|   |-- default.html
|   |-- post.html
|-- _posts
|   |-- 20011-10-25-open-source-is-good.markdown
|   |-- 20011-04-26-hello-world.markdown
|-- _site
|-- index.html
|-- assets
    |-- css
        |-- style.css
    |-- javascripts&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;_config.yml&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stores configuration data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;_includes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This folder is for partial views.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;_layouts&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This folder is for the main templates your content will be inserted into. You can have different layouts for different pages or page sections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;_posts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This folder contains your dynamic content/posts. the naming format is required to be &lt;code&gt;@YEAR-MONTH-DATE-title.MARKUP@&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;_site&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is where the generated site will be placed once Jekyll is done transforming it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;assets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This folder is not part of the standard jekyll structure. The assets folder represents &lt;em&gt;any generic&lt;/em&gt; folder you happen to create in your root directory. Directories and files not properly formatted for jekyll will be left untouched for you to serve normally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(read more: &lt;a href='https://github.com/mojombo/jekyll/wiki/Usage'&gt;https://github.com/mojombo/jekyll/wiki/Usage&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id='jekyll_configuration'&gt;Jekyll Configuration&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll supports various configuration options that are fully outlined here: &lt;a href='https://github.com/mojombo/jekyll/wiki/Configuration'&gt;https://github.com/mojombo/jekyll/wiki/Configuration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id='content_in_jekyll'&gt;Content in Jekyll&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Content in Jekyll is either a post or a page. These content &amp;#8220;objects&amp;#8221; get inserted into one or more templates to build the final output for its respective static-page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id='posts_and_pages'&gt;Posts and Pages&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both posts and pages should be written in markdown, textile, or HTML and may also contain Liquid templating syntax. Both posts and pages can have meta-data assigned on a per-page basis such as title, url path, as well as arbitrary custom meta-data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id='working_with_posts'&gt;Working With Posts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Creating a Post&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Posts are created by properly formatting a file and placing it the &lt;code&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; folder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formatting&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A post must have a valid filename in the form &lt;code&gt;YEAR-MONTH-DATE-title.MARKUP&lt;/code&gt; and be placed in the &lt;code&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. If the data format is invalid Jekyll will not recognize the file as a post. The date and title are automatically parsed from the filename of the post file. Additionally, each file must have &lt;a href='https://github.com/mojombo/jekyll/wiki/YAML-Front-Matter'&gt;YAML Front-Matter&lt;/a&gt; prepended to its content. YAML Front-Matter is a valid YAML syntax specifying meta-data for the given file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Order&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ordering is an important part of Jekyll but it is hard to specify a custom ordering strategy. Only reverse chronological and chronological ordering is supported in Jekyll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the date is hard-coded into the filename format, to change the order, you must change the dates in the filenames.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tags&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Posts can have tags associated with them as part of their meta-data. Tags may be placed on posts by providing them in the post&amp;#8217;s YAML front matter. You have access to the post-specific tags in the templates. These tags also get added to the sitewide collection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Categories&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Posts may be categorized by providing one or more categories in the YAML front matter. Categories offer more significance over tags in that they can be reflected in the URL path to the given post. Note categories in Jekyll work in a specific way. If you define more than one category you are defining a category hierarchy &amp;#8220;set&amp;#8221;. Example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;---
title :  Hello World
categories : [lessons, beginner]
---&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This defines the category hierarchy &amp;#8220;lessons/beginner&amp;#8221;. Note this is &lt;em&gt;one category&lt;/em&gt; node in Jekyll. You won&amp;#8217;t find &amp;#8220;lessons&amp;#8221; and &amp;#8220;beginner&amp;#8221; as two separate categories unless you define them elsewhere as singular categories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id='working_with_pages'&gt;Working With Pages&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Creating a Page&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pages are created by properly formatting a file and placing it anywhere in the root directory or subdirectories that do &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; start with an underscore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formatting&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to register as a Jekyll page the file must contain &lt;a href='https://github.com/mojombo/jekyll/wiki/YAML-Front-Matter'&gt;YAML Front-Matter&lt;/a&gt;. Registering a page means 1) that Jekyll will process the page and 2) that the page object will be available in the &lt;code&gt;site.pages&lt;/code&gt; array for inclusion into your templates.&lt;/p&gt;
>>>>>>> 1e9766a0981e238e709ef1e94f41625bbf6c7a54

&lt;p&gt;Joining a larger company is never easy and we learned a number of invaluable lessons along the way. We learned the importance of teamwork and a strong relationship with corporate leadership. We learned to leverage the innovations Conduit was creating, while adding our own unique voice, skills and capabilities to the Conduit team. Wibiya&amp;#8217;s team and technology are powering innovation across many Conduit products and has created a significant impact across the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Conduit’s new direction and organizational changes, the Wibiya platform is no longer in alignment with the future strategy. Over the coming months, most of the Wibiya team and innovations will be integrated throughout Conduit, bringing our expertise and experience to existing and yet-to-be released products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In appreciation of your loyalty, Conduit will be offering all Wibiya publishers three free months of Conduit Mobile. Conduit Mobile is a dynamic platform that allows anyone to easily create a mobile app or mobile site. Wibiya publishers will receive an email with additional information in a few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>What did I learn today?</title>
   <link href="/hello/2013/08/28/what-did-I-learn.html"/>
   <updated>2013-08-28T00:00:00+10:00</updated>
   <id>/hello/2013/08/28/what-did-I-learn</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;My emotional states shape my attitude. My attitude shapes my experience. When I smoke weed, I get a new perspective. When I use x, I am very happy, friendly and comfortable to be myself around people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The feelings emerge from using stimulants and they only there for a limited time. With the observing self, I can learn from these experiences and change consciously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although, I don&amp;#8217;t feel how I felt on Friday now, I can still remember it. I had the will and strength to dig deeper into the nagging feelings that I had around being with Anna and sex. Suddenly everything made sense. I don&amp;#8217;t remember how the thought process was but the feeling of peace, relaxation and love was right there. Here&amp;#8217;s what I can recall;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anna is a very important part of my life. I never wanted to have sex with someone although our sex life is hanging of the cliff. Thinking about someone feels like I am conflicting myself, although I don&amp;#8217;t know why yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a duty to myself to be the person that I want to be. I feel this is my opportunity to grow mindfully and be someone that I am 100% happy to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two are not conflicting with each other they are just tangled. There is a risk associated with changing personalities in terms maintaining my relationship with Anna. However, I feel like that risk can be mitigated if I keep the communication lines open with her and if she does the same too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Friday I was free from the nagging internal talk and I was happy. I don&amp;#8217;t know how but i even managed to hangout with people that didn&amp;#8217;t speak english. I had good time with my brothers and other people that we met casually.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class='highlight'&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class='ruby'&gt;&lt;span class='o'&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class='n'&gt;html&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class='o'&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;span class='k'&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class='nf'&gt;foo&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class='nb'&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class='s1'&gt;&amp;#39;foo&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class='k'&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>What did I learn, if I ever learned anything?</title>
   <link href="/hello/2013/08/28/test-test.html"/>
   <updated>2013-08-28T00:00:00+10:00</updated>
   <id>/hello/2013/08/28/test-test</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;My emotional states shape my attitude. My attitude shapes my experience. When I smoke weed, I get a new perspective. When I use x, I am very happy, friendly and comfortable to be myself around people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The feelings emerge from using stimulants and they only there for a limited time. With the observing self, I can learn from these experiences and change consciously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class='highlight'&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class='ruby'&gt;&lt;span class='lineno'&gt;1&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class='k'&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class='nf'&gt;foo&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class='lineno'&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;   &lt;span class='nb'&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class='s1'&gt;&amp;#39;foo&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class='lineno'&gt;3&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class='k'&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although, I don&amp;#8217;t feel how I felt on Friday now, I can still remember it. I had the will and strength to dig deeper into the nagging feelings that I had around being with Anna and sex. Suddenly everything made sense. I don&amp;#8217;t remember how the thought process was but the feeling of peace, relaxation and love was right there. Here&amp;#8217;s what I can recall;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anna is a very important part of my life. I never wanted to have sex with someone although our sex life is hanging of the cliff. Thinking about someone feels like I am conflicting myself, although I don&amp;#8217;t know why yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a duty to myself to be the person that I want to be. I feel this is my opportunity to grow mindfully and be someone that I am 100% happy to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two are not conflicting with each other they are just tangled. There is a risk associated with changing personalities in terms maintaining my relationship with Anna. However, I feel like that risk can be mitigated if I keep the communication lines open with her and if she does the same too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Friday I was free from the nagging internal talk and I was happy. I don&amp;#8217;t know how but i even managed to hangout with people that didn&amp;#8217;t speak english. I had good time with my brothers and other people that we met casually.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>